Guide to the School of Forestry and Environmental Studies, Yale University, Records Concerning the Industrial Forestry Seminar
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
School of Forestry and Environmental Studies, Yale University, records concerning the industrial forestry seminar
1955-1979
RU 44
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
3.25
(8 boxes)
The records consist of papers and materials from seminars and files from seminar instructors documenting the Industrial Forestry Seminar conducted by the Yale School of Forestry and Environmental Studies (called the School of Forestry prior to 1972).
Yale University. School of Forestry and Environmental Studies
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 24-E (YRG 24-E), Records of departments, offices, programs, and projects of the Yale School of Forestry.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the School of Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1982.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged in two series: I. Industrial Forestry Seminar Records, 1955-1979. II. Seminar Instructors, 1955-1971.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of papers and materials from seminars and files from seminar instructors documenting the Industrial Forestry Seminar conducted by the Yale School of Forestry and Environmental Studies (called the School of Forestry prior to 1972).
Conservation of natural resources; Environmental protection; Forest conservation; Forest management; Human ecology -- Study and teaching; Seminars; Yale University -- Curricula; Yale University -- Faculty; Yale University. School of Forestry; Industrial Forestry Seminar
- Records of the Industrial Forestry Seminar, 1955-1979; Accession 1982-A-016
  - Industrial Forestry Seminar
    - First, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Second, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Third, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Fourth, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Fifth, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Sixth, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Seventh, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Eighth, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Tenth, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Eleventh, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Twelfth, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 11 - 12)
    - Thirteenth, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Fourteenth, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Fifteenth, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Sixteenth, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Seventeenth, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Twenty-fourth, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Twenty-fifth, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Twenty-sixth, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Twenty-seventh, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Twenty-eighth, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Twenty-ninth, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Thirtieth, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Thirty-first, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Thirty-second, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 26 - 27)
    - Thirty-third, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 28 - 30)
    - Thirty-fourth, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 31 - 32)
    - Thirty-fifth, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Thirty-sixth, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 34 - 35)
    - Thirty-seventh, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Thirty-eighth, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 37 - 38)
    - Thirty-ninth, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 39 - 40)
    - Thirty-ninth, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 41 - 42)
    - Fortieth, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 43 - 44)
    - Forth-first & Forty-second, 1975-1979 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Miscellaneous, 1958-1972 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Seminar Instructors
    - Baker, G. O., Jr., 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 47 - 48)
    - Barclay, Henry I., Jr., 1959-1963 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Beggs, E. Kenneth, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Bormann, F. Herbert, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Burns, Garrett T., 1955 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Chesley, Kenneth G., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Cline, Charles E., 1968 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Clutter, Jerome L., 1969 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Condit, Gordon R., 1957 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Condrell, William K., 1969 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Connaughton, Charles, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Cunia, Tiberius, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Davis, Kenneth P., 1968 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Denton, John H., 1963 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Dickinson, F. E., 1960 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Duffield, J. A., 1956-1957 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Dumey, Arnold I., 1960 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Dunn, Paul M., 1955 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Falk, Harry W., 1957-1967 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Fedkiw, John, 1959-1967 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Ferguson, Eli, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Garratt, Rowland M., 1959 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Gillett, Charles A., undated (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Glascock, Hardy R., Jr., 1961 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Gordon, Jack, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Grimes, S. W., 1957 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Guttenplan, Sam, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Hall, Alfred, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Hall, Otis, F., 1961-1967 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Hall, R. C., 1955 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Hall, Robert M, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Hausberger, Robert V., 1961 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Heritage, Clark C., 1959 (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - Heyward, Frank, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Jensen, Herbert A., 1957 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Kane, Harry J., 1961-1963 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Keefe, Roger M., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Keith, John, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Knight, Vernon J., 1968 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Lauridsen, Morton J., 1961 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Leazenby, Arthur J., 1961 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Lininger, Paul, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Locke, Edward G., 1957 (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Lund, C.J.H., 1960 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Maki, T.E., 1957 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Manson, Byrne C., 1959 (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Mason, David T., 1961 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - McClaren, C. G., 1960 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - McCourt, Arthur (& Swenson), 1959 (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Mead, Walter J., 1965 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Mergen, Francois, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Meyer, Walter H., 1959 (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Mihailoff, N.V., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - Miles, John, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - Miller, Frank B., 1959 (Box 7, Folder 102)
    - Miller, James F., 1961 (Box 7, Folder 103)
    - Moise, William L., 1960-1964 (Box 7, Folder 104)
    - Nelson, Arthur W., Jr., 1963 (Box 7, Folder 105)
    - Olsen, Paul, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 106)
    - Orell, Bernard L., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 107)
    - Payne, B. H., 1960 (Box 7, Folder 108)
    - Perlnutter, Howard J., undated (Box 7, Folder 109)
    - Peterson, Ervin L., 1961 (Box 7, Folder 110)
    - Poletika, N.V., 1959 (Box 7, Folder 111)
    - Reynolds, R. R., 1959 (Box 7, Folder 112)
    - Ross, Lawrence A., 1969 (Box 7, Folder 113)
    - Saxon, O. Glenn, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 114)
    - Schultz, Freeman, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 115)
    - Segur, J. A., 1960-1971 (Box 7, Folder 116)
    - Silversides, C. Ross, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 117)
    - Smith, Kenneth, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 118)
    - Spates, Thomas G., 1959 (Box 7, Folder 119)
    - Sperry, Ronald D., 1963 (Box 7, Folder 120)
    - Staebuer, RaIph C., 1959 (Box 7, Folder 121)
    - Sutlive, Kurt, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 122)
    - Swenning, Karl A., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 123)
    - Taylor, Donald W., 1962 (Box 8, Folder 124)
    - Taylor, John L., 1962 (Box 8, Folder 125)
    - Thomas, Sydney F., 1960 (Box 8, Folder 126)
    - Tillotson, Mitchell, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 127)
    - Tornlinson, Harry T., 1962 (Box 8, Folder 128)
    - Trescott, John H., Jr., 1965 (Box 8, Folder 129)
    - Vanx, H. J., 1960 (Box 8, Folder 130)
    - Warnback, Robert, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 131)
    - Welch, William D., 1959 (Box 8, Folder 132)
    - Wesson, William H., Jr., 1959 (Box 8, Folder 133)
    - Whitaker, Meade, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 134)
    - Williams, Ellis T., 1965 (Box 8, Folder 135)
    - Yoder, Ray A., 1961 (Box 8, Folder 136)